writings
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- writings, 2.1.9.3
  - So Long until Tomorrow [includes color photographs], undated; 7 (Box 1612)
    - Another degree, this time at the University of Vermont, 1
    - Verso: Another degree, this time at the University of Vermont, 1-verso
    - L.T., Jr. and his B-25 [more written semi-legibly], 2
    - Verso: L.T. Jr. and his B-25 [more written semi-legibly], 2-verso
    - L.T. Jr., (an his flying pal Ed Seiler) find first world flight flagship on mountain in Alaska where it crashed in 1924., 3
    - Verso: L.T. Jr., (an his flying pal Ed Seiler) find first world flight flagship on mountain in Alaska where it crashed in 1924., 3-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas posing with his hat on his knee in front of old building], 4
    - [Close-up of Lowell Thomas], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas walking among a crowd of people], 6
    - The History of Civilization Fireplace., 7
    - Verso: The History of Civilization Fireplace., 7-verso
    - L.T. Jr. and his mother [Frances Ryan Thomas], 8
    - Verso: L.T. Jr. and his mother, 8-verso
    - One of my favorite pictures [Close-up of Frances Ryan Thomas], 9
    - Verso: One of my favorite pictures, 9-verso
    - Please cut me out - L. T.; Fran and Sun Oil Tycoon Joe Pew., 10
    - Verso: Please cut me out - L. T.; Fran and Sun Oil Tycoon Joe Pew., 10-verso
    - L.T. Sr. in Assam on a search for a man-eating tiger., 11
    - Verso: L.T. Sr. in Assam on a search for a man-eating tiger., 11-verso
    - How do you like the outfit? Riding on an elephant in the royal procession wearing tails and a top hat!, 12
    - Verso: How do you like the outfit? Riding on an elephant in the royal procession wearing tails and a top hat!, 12-verso
    - Father Ross, who for two years conducted Mass, while holding a 6-gun under his cassack., 13
    - Verso: Father Ross, who for two years conducted Mass, while holding a 6-gun under his cassack., 13-verso
  - So Long until Tomorrow, undated; 8 (Box 1612)
    - Count Felix von Luckner, "The Sea Devil," whom Gen. Patton saved from the Russians., 1
    - Verso: Count Felix von Luckner, "The Sea Devil," whom Gen. Patton saved from the Russians., 1-verso
    - Fred Wather[?], 2
    - Verso: Fred Wather[?], 2-verso
    - Cooper 18D[?], 3
    - Verso: Cooper 18D[?], 3-verso
    - The Marquis degli Albizzi, super-athlete., 4
    - Verso: The Marqius degli Albizzi, super-athlete., 4-verso
    - Reeves, 5
    - Verso: Reeves, 5-verso
    - With Taunegs, Timbuetee. Southern Sahara [Tuaregs?], 6
    - Verso: With Taunegs, Timbuetee. Southern Sahara, 6-verso
  - So Long until Tomorrow (Prosper Buranelli), undated; 9 (Box 1612)
    - Prosper prepares to bolt from THIS IS YOUR LIFE show.; L.T. with Prosper Buranelli and Ralph Edwards ("This Is Your Life"), 1
    - Verso: Prosper prepares to bolt from THIS IS YOUR LIFE show.; L.T. with Prosper Buranelli and Ralph Edwards ("This Is Your Life"), 1-verso
  - So Long until Tomorrow (President Dwight D. Eisenhower), undated; 10 (Box 1612)
    - Washn. D.C. - Flanked by Harry Kaluime (left) Vice President of Warner Bors., + Lowell Thomas, Pres. Eishenhower is shown arriving at a Washington Cinema to view a special private showing of Cinerame" 7/6/55; President Eisenhower, one of the many millions who came to see Cinerama, the process than created a screen revolution, 1
    - Verso: Washn. D.C. - Flanked by Harry Kaluime (left) Vice President of Warner Bors., + Lowell Thomas, Pres. Eishenhower is shown arriving at a Washington Cinema to view a special private showing of Cinerame" 7/6/55; President Eisenhower, one of the many millions who came to see Cinerama, the process than created a screen revolution, 1-verso
    - [L.T. with Eisenhower, circa 1940s], 2
  - So Long until Tomorrow (Hammersley Hill), undated; 11 (Box 1612)
    - Hammersley Hill, which has had only two owners since Queen Anne made it a grant to the Hammersley family, more than 200 years ago., 1
    - Verso: Hammersley Hill, which has had only two owners since Queen Anne made it a grant to the Hammersley family, more than 200 years ago., 1-verso
    - [Hammersley Hill], 2
  - So Long until Tomorrow (President Herbert Hoover), undated; 12 (Box 1612)
    - President Hoover and my Dad., 1
    - Verso: President Hoover and my Dad., 1-verso
    - [Herbert Hoover], 2
  - So Long until Tomorrow (T. E. Lawrence), undated; 13 (Box 1612)
    - T.E. Lawrence on his racing camel. In battle he accidently shot it in the head., 1
    - Verso: T.E. Lawrence on his racing camel. In battle he accidently shot it in the head., 1-verso
  - So Long until Tomorrow (Jayne Mansfield), undated; 14 (Box 1612)
    - L.T. + Jayne Mansfield, 1
    - Verso: L.T. + Jayne Mansfield, 1-verso
  - So Long until Tomorrow: From Quaker Hill to Kathmandu by Lowell Thomas (Nepal), undated; 15 (Box 1612)
    - King of Nepal - Diamond Crown + Bird of Paradise; Mahendra Bir Bikram Shah Deva, King of Shangri La, wearing his crown of diamonds, emeralds, rubies and the white plume of the Bird of Paradise, 1
    - Verso: King of Nepal - Diamond Crown + Bird of Paradise; Mahendra Bir Bikram Shah Deva, King of Shangri La, wearing his crown of diamonds, emeralds, rubies and the white plume of the Bird of Paradise, 1-verso
    - The priceless birds of paradise sunbursts we presented to the King and Queen of Nepal at Kathmandu, 2
    - Verso: The priceless birds of paradise sunbursts we presented to the King and Queen of Nepal at Kathmandu, 2-verso
  - So Long until Tomorrow: From Quaker Hill to Kathmandu by Lowell Thomas (New Guinea), undated; 16 (Box 1612)
    - With Canibals in New Guinea the man who came to dinner, and then decided to run like H.-, 1
    - Verso: With Canibals in New Guinea the man who came to dinner, and then decided to run like H.-, 1-verso
  - So Long until Tomorrow: From Quaker Hill to Kathmandu by Lowell Thomas (Petra), undated; 17 (Box 1612)
    - A rose-red temple carved like a cameo from the face of the mountain. (only to be used by permission of Lowell Thomas), 1
    - Verso: A rose-red temple carved like a cameo from the face of the mountain. (only to be used by permission of Lowell Thomas), 1-verso
    - "Pharaoh's Treasury" or the "Temple of Isis" (only to be used by permission of Lowell Thomas), 2
    - Verso: "Pharaoh's Treasury" or the "Temple of Isis" (only to be used by permission of Lowell Thomas), 2-verso
  - So Long until Tomorrow: From Quaker Hill to Kathmandu by Lowell Thomas (Skiing), undated; 18 (Box 1612)
    - John Gow, a champion skier in spite of having lost both legs. He is following me., 1
    - Note: John Gow, a champion skier in spite of having lost both legs. He is following me., 2
    - When I tried in vain to make skiers of two ex-heavyweight champions: -Eddie Eagan (amateure); and Gene Tunny, the legendary pro, 3
    - Note: When I tried in vain to make skiers of two ex-heavyweight champions: -Eddie Eagan (amateure); and Gene Tunny, the legendary pro, 4
    - Ski champion Toni Matt, the only skier ever to schuss[?] the Mt. Washington precipice known as the Tuckerman Headwall., 5
    - Verso: Ski champion Toni Matt, the only skier ever to schuss[?] the Mt. Washington precipice known as the Tuckerman Headwall., 5-verso
    - Erling Strom, conquerer of Mt. McKinley, with a ski companion, 6
    - Verso: Erling Strom, conquerer of Mt. McKinley, with a ski companion, 6-verso
    - Sig Buchmayr executes an acrobatic jump on the Tuckerman Headwall, 7
    - Verso: Sig Buchmayr executes an acrobatic jump on the Tuckerman Headwall, 7-verso
    - I prefer this one. But cut off woman on left an the two on right. Caption: - Jim Parker (skis) who was last in the unexplored rapids of the Indus. On right, Chris Young, co-star with Jim in Search for Paradise, 8
    - Verso: I prefer this one. But cut off woman on left an the two on right. Caption: - Jim Parker (skis) who was last in the unexplored rapids of the Indus. On right, Chris Young, co-star with Jim in Search for Paradise, 8-verso
  - So Long until Tomorrow: From Quaker Hill to Kathmandu by Lowell Thomas (Jim Thorpe), undated; 19 (Box 1612)
    - Many believe him to have been the greatest all around athlete of all time, the legendary Jim Thorpe, with Lowell Jr, at the Taft School, 1
    - Verso: Many believe him to have been the greatest all around athlete of all time, the legendary Jim Thorpe, with Lowell Jr, at the Taft School, 1-verso
  - So Long until Tomorrow: From Quaker Hill to Kathmandu by Lowell Thomas (Tibet), undated; 20 (Box 1612)
    - The Potala - one of the wonders of the world. Almost as lofty as the Empire State Building built without elevators and no steel. Polata-reflection. A few pedestrians in fore.[ground], 1
    - Verso: The Potala - one of the wonders of the world. Almost as lofty as the Empire State Building built without elevators and no steel. Polata-reflection. A few pedestrians in fore.[ground], 1-verso
    - L.T. Jr., Rimshi Kyipup, Luishahr Djoza Lama, Secretary of War, Dorje Changwaba and L.T. Sr., 2
    - Verso: L.T. Jr., Rimshi Kyipup, Luishahr Djoza Lama, Secretary of War, Dorje Changwaba and L.T. Sr., 2-verso
    - Each evening we paid our men who had provided the caravan for that day, 3
    - Verso: Each evening we paid our men who had provided the caravan for that day, 3-verso
    - After the accident, homeward bound -- hopefully -- across the lofty Tibetan plateau, while his bearers chanted: "Oh Lord Buddha, lighten out load!", 4
    - Verso: After the accident, homeward bound -- hopefully -- across the lofty Tibetan plateau, while his bearers chanted: "Oh Lord Buddha, lighten out load!", 4-verso
    - First broadcast ever made from Tibet. Also, the first ever made anywhere with battery equipment.; L.T. Sr. recording a broadcast by candlelight, in a dark bungalow on the way to Lhasa. 1st ever in Tibet - and 1st anywhere with battery equipment., 5
    - Verso: First broadcast ever made from Tibet. Also, the first ever made anywhere with battery equipment.; L.T. Sr. recording a broadcast by candlelight, in a dark bungalow on the way to Lhasa. 1st ever in Tibet - and 1st anywhere with battery equipment., 5-verso
    - Dalai Lama on an outdoor throne. On the right, Tokra, a high lama selected to rule until Dalai Lama came of age., 6
    - Verso: Dalai Lama on an outdoor throne. On the right, Tokra, a high lama selected to rule until Dalai Lama came of age., 6-verso
    - His Holiness, age 16 on his throne at Norbu Linga. The Lord Chamberlain on right, 7
    - Verso: His Holiness, age 16 on his throne at Norbu Linga. The Lord Chamberlain on right, 7-verso
    - Injured Newscaster Returns with Message fro Truman New York Noted author and newscaster Lowell Thomas (center), who was injured when he was thrown by a horse on a Tibetian mountain pass, is shown being greeted by his father, Dr. Harry C. Thomas, 8
    - Verso: Injured Newscaster Returns with Message fro Truman New York Noted author and newscaster Lowell Thomas (center), who was injured when he was thrown by a horse on a Tibetian mountain pass, is shown being greeted by his father, Dr. Harry C. Thomas, on his arrival, with his son, Lowell, Jr. (left), at LaGuardia Airport today. Thomas told newsmen that after his injury, he was carried for 16 days and nights by native bearers to a town where he could recieve medical aid. Although his injury has been diagnosed as a broken thigh bone, he is able to walk on crutches. Also, Thomas is carrying a personal message from the Tibetian government to President Truman along with an official scroll from the Dalai Lama, the boy ruler of the inaccessible nation. Thomas is believed the first westerner in history to be given such a message from the religious rulers of Tibet. MCS 10/16/49, 8-verso
    - Note: [envelope] We return from Tibet, and are met by my father, 9
  - So Long until Tomorrow: From Quaker Hill to Kathmandu by Lowell Thomas (Bertha Spafford Vester), undated; 21 (Box 1612)
    - Bertha Vester, a modern Florence Nightingale whose humanitarian work spanned some seven decades., 1
    - Verso: Bertha Vester, a modern Florence Nightingale whose humanitarian work spanned some seven decades., 1-verso
    - Note: Bertha Vester, 2
  - So Long until Tomorrow: From Quaker Hill to Kathmandu by Lowell Thomas (World War II), undated; 22 (Box 1612)
    - [L.T. with General Patton], 1
    - [L.T. with Chiang Kai-Shek], 2
    - Captain Eddie (Rickenbacker) and General Jimmy (Doolittle) help me celebrate an anniversary, 3
    - Note: Captain Eddie (Rickenbacker) and General Jimmy (Doolittle) help me celebrate an anniversary, 4
  - Commander Grow, circa early 1930s; 23 (Box 1612)
    - Study in Contrasts [semi-legible] note the plane in the back - a forced landing in a rever bed - [?] in a storm. [?], 1
    - Verso: Study in Contrasts [semi-legible] note the plane in the back - a forced landing in a rever bed - [?] in a storm. [?], 1-verso
    - In camp on my [?] Azupizin[?], 2
    - Verso: in camp on my [?] Azupizin[?], 2-verso
    - 86- Crossing the Aquippa[?] rivers at Aquippign[? - Exploration. Fording streams on the trail, 3
    - Verso: 86- Crossing the Aquippa[?] rivers at Aquippign[? - Exploration. Fording streams on the trail, 3-verso
    - Up stream in canoe 1 mile an hour - The use paddles going down., 4
    - Verso: up stream in canoe 1 mile an hour - The use paddles going down., 4-verso
    - 83 [?] a white chief not [?]- note the wad of Coca in each cheek, 5
    - Verso: 83 [?] a white chief not [?]- note the wad of Coca in each cheek, 5-verso
  - The Never Neverland Back of the Beyond by Lowell Thomas, circa late 1950s; 24 (Box 1612)
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with two other men], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with three other men], 2
    - [Men climbing down rocky side with camera equipment, Lowell Thomas toward center], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas standing on rocky hillside], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas wiping sweat from his brow], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas talking with another man], 6
    - [Lowell Thomas, second from right, in group picture], 7
  - These Men Shall Never Die by Lowell Thomas, circa 1940s; 25 (Box 1612)
    - The Battle of Coral Sea: Japanese Aircraft Carrier, Ryukaku. Note U.S. Navy torpedo plans veering off to the right after dropping aerial torpedo (white splash, right center.), 1
    - Verso: The Battle of Coral Sea: Japanese Aircraft Carrier, Ryukaku. Note U.S. Navy torpedo plans veering off to the right after dropping aerial torpedo (white splash, right center.), 1-verso
    - June 12, 1942 - The Battle of the Coral Sea: (k) The Japanese Aircraft Carrier, Ryukaku being circled by three U.S. Navy torpedo planes, which are closing in for another attack., 2
    - Verso: June 12, 1942 - The Battle of the Coral Sea: (k) The Japanese Aircraft Carrier, Ryukaku being circled by three U.S. Navy torpedo planes, which are closing in for another attack., 2-verso
    - Sept. 7, 1942 - Battle of Midway, June 4th, 5th and 6th, 1942: General view of burning oil tanks on Midway Island after they were hit by Japanese bombs. Note the gooney birds in the foreground., 3
    - Verso: Sept. 7, 1942 - Battle of Midway, June 4th, 5th and 6th, 1942: General view of burning oil tanks on Midway Island after they were hit by Japanese bombs. Note the gooney birds in the foreground., 3-verso
    - Sept. 7, 1942 - Battle of Midway, June 4th, 5th and 6th, 1942: A general view of the damage done on Midway Island before the Japanese raiders were beaten off., 4
    - Verso: Sept. 7, 1942 - Battle of Midway, June 4th, 5th and 6th, 1942: A general view of the damage done on Midway Island before the Japanese raiders were beaten off., 4-verso
    - Sept. 7, 1942 - Battle of Midway, June 4th, 5th and 6th, 1942: This is what was left of a Japanese Zero plane shot down on Midway during the raid., 5
    - Verso: Sept. 7, 1942 - Battle of Midway, June 4th, 5th and 6th, 1942: This is what was left of a Japanese Zero plane shot down on Midway during the raid., 5-verso
    - Sept. 7, 1942 - Battle of Midway, June 4th, 5th and 6th, 1942: The interior of one of the hangers on Midway Island, damaged during the raid., 6
    - Verso: Sept. 7, 1942 - Battle of Midway, June 4th, 5th and 6th, 1942: The interior of one of the hangers on Midway Island, damaged during the raid., 6-verso
    - Sept. 7, 1942 - Battle of Midway, June 4th, 5th and 6th, 1942: "There go the Marines!" Marine bombers take off from Midway Island to intercept the enemy coming to attack this American outpost., 7
    - Verso: Sept. 7, 1942 - Battle of Midway, June 4th, 5th and 6th, 1942: "There go the Marines!" Marine bombers take off from Midway Island to intercept the enemy coming to attack this American outpost., 7-verso
    - December 21, 1942 - Stricken Japanese Cargo Ships - Four plumes of smoke, one just barely discernible on the horizon near the tip of the island in the background, arise from as many Japanese cargo vessels destroyed by U.S. forces in the Battle of Guadalcanal. The vessels were found beached at Tassafaronga, about 7 1/2 miles west of U.S. positions on Guadalcanal November 15, 1942 and were destroyed by bombs, artillery and naval gun fire. In addition the enemy lost 11 warships, including one battleship, and eight transports and suffered damage to seven other wasships. American losses in the battle were two light cruisers and six destroyers., 8
    - Verso: December 21, 1942 - Stricken Japanese Cargo Ships - Four plumes of smoke, one just barely discernible on the horizon near the tip of the island in the background, arise from as many Japanese cargo vessels destroyed by U.S. forces in the Battle of Guadalcanal. The vessels were found beached at Tassafaronga, about 7 1/2 miles west of U.S. positions on Guadalcanal November 15, 1942 and were destroyed by bombs, artillery and naval gun fire. In addition the enemy lost 11 warships, including one battleship, and eight transports and suffered damage to seven other wasships. American losses in the battle were two light cruisers and six destroyers., 8-verso
    - December 28, 1942 - Japanese transports, hit by U.S. surface ships and aircraft, are seen beached and burning at Tassafaronge, seven and one half miles from American positions on Guadalcanal, on November 16, 1942. They were the only ships to reach the island of a powerful Japanese fleet which attempted a mass attack on Guadalcanal, but which was crushed in the fleet actions of Nov. 12-15., 9
    - Verso: December 28, 1942 - Japanese transports, hit by U.S. surface ships and aircraft, are seen beached and burning at Tassafaronge, seven and one half miles from American positions on Guadalcanal, on November 16, 1942. They were the only ships to reach the island of a powerful Japanese fleet which attempted a mass attack on Guadalcanal, but which was crushed in the fleet actions of Nov. 12-15., 9-verso
    - An American task force is shown while being attached from the air in the Battle of Santa Cruz, Oct. 26, 1942. A Carrier on the right is sharply turning. The U.S. destroyer SMITH (center) has just been struck by a burning, falling Japanese plane. On the left two screening vessels are seen., 10
    - Verso: An American task force is shown while being attached from the air in the Battle of Santa Cruz, Oct. 26, 1942. A Carrier on the right is sharply turning. The U.S. destroyer SMITH (center) has just been struck by a burning, falling Japanese plane. On the left two screening vessels are seen., 10-verso
    - HAVOC--Carnage wrought among Japanese attackers who tried unsuccessfully to storm Marines machine gun positions during Battle of Tenaru River, August 21, 1942., 11
    - Verso: HAVOC--Carnage wrought among Japanese attackers who tried unsuccessfully to storm Marines machine gun positions during Battle of Tenaru River, August 21, 1942., 11-verso
  - These Men Shall Never Die by Lowell Thomas, circa 1940s; 26 (Box 1612)
    - 5th Air Force, 1
    - Verso: 5th Air Force, 1-verso
    - Lt. Col. Merritt A. Edson, USMC, 2
    - Verso: Lt. Col. Merritt A. Edson, USMC, 2-verso
    - Ensign Francis R. Register U.S.N.R., 3
    - Verso: Ensign Francis R. Register U.S.N.R., 3-verso
    - Schmidt, Albert Andrew, U.S. Marine Corps., 4
    - Verso: Schmidt, Albert Andrew, U.S. Marine Corps., 4-verso
    - Verso: Comdr. H.J. Schonland U.S.N., 5
    - Comdr. H.J. Schonland U.S.N., 5-verso
    - 1. Lieutenant Harold H. (Swede) Larsen, commander of the Navy's famous Torpedo Squadron Eight, has been on Pacific duty since before Pearl Harbor. His squadron has just completed four months active duty off Guadalcanal during which only one plane was lost in 27 attacks on Nipponese ships and positions. The ribbons on his breast include those of the Navy Cross and the Distinguished Flying Cross.", 6
    - Verso: 1. Lieutenant Harold H. (Swede) Larsen, commander of the Navy's famous Torpedo Squadron Eight, has been on Pacific duty since before Pearl Harbor. His squadron has just completed four months active duty off Guadalcanal during which only one plane was lost in 27 attacks on Nipponese ships and positions. The ribbons on his breast include those of the Navy Cross and the Distinguished Flying Cross.", 6-verso
    - Maj. John F. Dobbin, 7
    - Verso: Maj. John F. Dobbin, 7-verso
    - Only Navy Nurse to Escape from Corregidor - Miss Ann Agnes Bernatitus, USNNC, the only Navy nurse to escape from Bataan and the siege of Corregidor, left the Manila Bay fortress on a submarine two days before the surrender. She returned to this country only a few days ago., 8
    - Verso: Only Navy Nurse to Escape from Corregidor - Miss Ann Agnes Bernatitus, USNNC, the only Navy nurse to escape from Bataan and the siege of Corregidor, left the Manila Bay fortress on a submarine two days before the surrender. She returned to this country only a few days ago., 8-verso
    - January 2, 1943 - This is machinist Donald E. Runyon, USN, of Fighting Squadron Six, who shot down eight Japanese planes in aerial combat during the month of August, 1942. He bagged four of the planes in a single day. Runyon lives in Ellisville, Miss., 9
    - Verso: January 2, 1943 - This is machinist Donald E. Runyon, USN, of Fighting Squadron Six, who shot down eight Japanese planes in aerial combat during the month of August, 1942. He bagged four of the planes in a single day. Runyon lives in Ellisville, Miss., 9-verso
    - Lieut. Comr. Frank W. Fenno, Jr. USN, 10
    - Verso: Lieut. Comr. Frank W. Fenno, Jr. USN, 10-verso
    - Major Walter C. Beckham, De Funiak Springs, Fla. (Missing) Fifty-seven combat missions. 123:20 combat hours. Eighteen enemy planes destroyed. Distinguished Service Cross, Silver Star, Distunguished Flying Cross with three clusters, Air Medal with three clusters., 11
    - Note: Major Walter C. Beckham, De Funiak Springs, Fla. (Missing) Fifty-seven combat missions. 123:20 combat hours. Eighteen enemy planes destroyed. Distinguished Service Cross, Silver Star, Distunguished Flying Cross with three clusters, Air Medal with three clusters., 12
    - Colonel Duncan and Major Beckham chatting at the snack bar after a mission., 13
    - Note: Colonel Duncan and Major Beckham chatting at the snack bar after a mission., 14
    - Walter C. Beckham, 15
    - Verso: Walter C. Beckham, 15-verso
    - Maj. Walter Beckham, 16
    - Verso: Maj. Walter Beckham, 16-verso
    - 1st Lt. David C. Waybur Cavalry. 3rd Reconnaissance Troop, 3rd Infantry Div., USA, 17
    - Verso: 1st Lt. David C. Waybur Cavalry. 3rd Reconnaissance Troop, 3rd Infantry Div., USA, 17-verso
    - LT. + J.G. Nicholas Nooy, 18
    - Verso: LT. + J.G. Nicholas Nooy, 18-verso
    - LT. J.G. Nicholas Nooy, 19
    - Verso: LT. J.G. Nicholas Nooy, 19-verso
    - Lieutenant Junior Grade Nicholas Nooy, 20
    - Verso: Lieutenant Junior Grade Nicholas Nooy, 20-verso
    - Pvt. Joseph Martinez, 21
    - Verso: Pvt. Joseph Martinez, 21-verso
    - Joe Martinez, Right cartrage belt on shoulder, 22